Guide to the Pauline Park Papers TAM.663
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Events, 1990-2014, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 4.5 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing.; 282 Megabytes in 89 computer files.; 2 audiocassettes
  - Speaking Engagements 2001, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Engagements 2002, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NewFest Programs, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 1, Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Speaking Engagements 2003, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Event Flyers and Programs, 2004-2015, undated; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Law 2004: Engaging Our Diverse Communities, 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - New York State Dignity for All Students Forum: Press, 2004; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Park, P. v. Advantage Security et al, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Speaking Engagements 2004, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 5, 6)
  - 2005 New York City Pride March: Grand Marshall, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Event Posters and Flyers, 2005-2014, undated; 1 folder (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS007, Folder 11)
  - Speaking Engagements 2005, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 3, 4)
  - Event Programs, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Registered Nurse Training and Upgrading Fund: Gender 101 Program Evaluation Forms, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Speaking Engagements 2006, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 1, 2)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Day of Silence and Breaking the Silence Rally: Images, 2006 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_TAM_663_ER_1)
  - Rhonda Schaller Studio Press Release, 2007; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Engagements 2007, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 6, 7)
  - Speaking Engagements 2008, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 4, 5)
  - Speaking Engagements 2009, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 2, 3)
  - Transgender Training for Puente Para La Salud, 2009; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Speaking Engagements 2010, 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 15, Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Speaking Engagements 2011, 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 13, 14)
  - Speaking Engagements 2012, 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 11, 12)
  - Speaking Engagements 2013, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Speeches and Speaker Biographies, 2013; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Engagements 2014, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Engagements, undated; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Series IV. Personal, 1994-2015, undated; 1.25 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 flat box.; 3 audiocassettes; 3 videocassettes (vhs)
  This series is grouped by file title, then arranged in alphabetical order.
  This series mostly contains material about Pauline Park's life that was created by other writers or artists. While most of the material comes from press about Park, there are also a significant number of interviews with, and documentaries about, Pauline Park. Material in this series includes: VHS tapes, audiocassette recordings of interviews with Park, written interviews with Park, publications, correspondence, award plaques with related program, and press.
  - 1994 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1997 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1999 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 2000 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 2001 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 2004 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2005 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2006 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 2007 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2008 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2009 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 2010 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 2011 Press Coverage, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Academic Articles on Homosexuality and Islam, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Activities and Correspondence, 1998-2015, undated; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Award Plaques: Transworld III Conference and Translatina Community, 2001-2002; 1 box (Box 7)
  - Award and Special Recognition, 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2012-2015, undated; 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 10, Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Nasser, Sana, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Embodying Asian/American Sexualities Interview, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Interviews, 2005-2006; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 3, 4)
  - Letters to Pauline Park, 2005; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Press: "The Glass is Half Full, Mostly" (Park Quoted), 2003; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 2005-2015; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Program: "Who is Pauline Park?" Documentary, 2012; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Programs, Flyers, and Brochures: "Envisioning Justice" Documentary, 2008-2011; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Publications Profiling Pauline Park, 2000-2013, undated; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 13, 14)
  - Resume, undated; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - WBAI New York Transgender Coalition on Sexual Orientation Non-Discrimination Act (2.5.2002) and Pauline Park on NYAGRA and Sexual Orientation Non-Discrimination Act (2.10.2002), cuid36928 (Box 8, Cassette 663.006)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 52 minutes
  - Sound Recording: "The Transgender Experience (Out FM, WBAI, 12.22.2003) -- Park, Pauline, Dean Spade, and Tommy Wang", 2003-12-22 (Box 8, Cassette 663.004)
  - Sound Recordings: "Out FM Program (WBAI, 11.26.2000) -- Park, Pauline, Stuart Chen-Hayes, Tina Benez and WBAI News Interview with Pauline Park on Int. No. 754 (3.14.2001)", 2000-2001 (Box 8, Cassette 663.010)
  - Tamiment Correspondence, 2015; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Video Recording: "In The Life American Gender Episode # 1406 - March 2005 TRT 56:47 minutes", 1 folder (Box 8, Video 663.013)
  - Video Recording: "POCAHONTAS (featuring Pauline Park) Director: Ho Tam 1998" (Box 8, Video 663.011)
  - Video Recording: "Sexandthespirit.net", undated (Box 8, Video 663.012)